<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[John Ripke | Front-end Developer & UX Designer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, I am John Ripke a Dutch front-end developer & UX Designer.]]></description><link>https://johnripke.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 15:50:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Hello my name is John...]]></title><description><![CDATA[an award-winning Dutch front-end developer & UX designer living in some place, the Netherlands. By day I sculpt online magic at Syndia. And…]]></description><link>https://johnripke.com/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://johnripke.com/about/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;an award-winning Dutch front-end developer &amp;#x26; UX designer living in some place, the Netherlands. By day I sculpt online magic at Syndia. And by night I like to wander around in the ever evolving landscapes of front-end development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been designing for the last 2 years and got into developing about 1 years ago. I tend to spend the most of my time working with CSS, HTML and Javascript and feel quite comfortable using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website is like a digital playground to me. A place where I can explore new things and share them in a way I wished they where explained to me. I learn from the community and love to share what I have learned back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I’m not building websites I love spending time with my family and friends. Listening to some quality music, writing, fitness or running. Oohw and when I feel inspired and got some spare time left also got some aspirations in making music myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More questions about me or want to chat? The quickest way is through Twitter at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/johnripke&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@johnripke&lt;/a&gt;. Need more words? Feel free to shoot me an e-mail at johnripke @ gmail dot com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also find me on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/syndia&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; where I share code, &lt;a href=&quot;https://nl.linkedin.com/in/johnripke&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; for professional matters and &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/user/johnripke&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; for listening to quality music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;About this website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although I plan on writing a post on how I’ve made this site from scratch in the near future. I would like to give a shout out to all the fantastic services helped me building it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website is written in HTML, CSS and Javascript. Compiled by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gatsby&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.styled-components.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Styled Components&lt;/a&gt;. Hosted on &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt; and version controlled by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. The fonts used are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/fonts/specimen/PT+Serif&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;PT Serif&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/fonts/specimen/PT+Sans&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;PT Sans&lt;/a&gt; served by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/fonts&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google Fonts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>